好吧那怎么样
All right, how was that?
对你们中的某些人来说可能有点困难。
For some of you that was
probably a bit challenging.
对你们中的某些人来说是粉碎了
For some of you, crushed it.
很容易劳尔不上
Rolled through it easily.
为了诚实和公平，我也做了这个密码挑战。
So in the interest of honesty and
fairness, I also did this code challenge.
我以前没做过
I did not do it before.
我自己写的，但是在我解决的时候才解决的。
I wrote it up, but I didn't solve it until
I was solving the same time you were.
这是我的解决方案。
Here is my solution.
这就是一般的 blah， blah， blah.
So here's the general blah, blah, blah.
我不修改这个
I don't modify this.
我创造了这个
I created this.
那么其他的解决方案都是我完成后的生活代码
So every other solution I will
live code after I've done but
我是个变慢的打字员
this one I'm a slow typist.
相信我是我干的
So just trust me that I did it.
我没作弊
I didn't cheat.
我甚至在此放弃了我的谷歌查询，因为我也需要帮助。
I even here I left up my Google
queries because I also need help.
我不记得这些事了
I don't remember these things.
我不完美
I'm not perfect.
我也得查这些东西
I had to look up this stuff too.
所以我的解决方案就是我创造了一个阶级。
So my solution was I created a class.
我知道这需要某种形式的元素
And I know that it takes
an element of some sort,
食物数据不按顺序排列
it takes food data doesn't
matter on the order.
我只是在创造范围内的人
And I'm just creating those in the scope.
我创建了一个叫做渲染列表的函数。
I created a function called render list.
其实这最后一次是我最不想担心的事了
Actually did this last cuz it's probably
the last thing I need to worry about.
但我所做的是我知道我需要创建一个项目的清单。
But what I did was I knew that I
needed to create a list of items.
我不想在这个功能上做这个。
And I didn't want to do
that in this one function.
因此，我创建了一个称为 createFoodItems的单独函数。
So I created this separate
function called createFoodItems.
那么在这个问题上，是这个挑战，还是
Now, on this question,
was this challenging, or
是中间的吗
was it sort of in the middle?
在中间的索塔挑战吗
Sorta in the middle, challenging?
对于很多人来说，这通常是一种代码问题的风格
For a lot of people, and this is generally
the kind of the style of code question I
就像你非常，非常，非常依赖框架或者
like, it's are you very, very,
very dependent on frameworks or
你能理解我能创造一个元素的基本要素
do you understand kinda the basics
of can I create an element,
我能创造一个终结收听者之类的吗
can I create an end listener and
things like that?
这就是为什么我要问这个问题。
That's why I like to ask this question.
我不关心具体的框架知识或专业知识。
Is I don't care about specific
framework knowledge or expertise.
你可以成为世界上最顶尖的反应专家
You could be the world's
leading a react expert.
您是否可以创建将内容呈示到 DOM中的 HTML 页面 ?
Can you create an HTML page that
renders stuff into the dom?
就这样了
That's it.
要用我必须用的创造元素，那就是我的去，对，
And to use that I had to use create
element, which is my go to, yes,
我正在使用 &lt;div&gt;。
I'm using a &lt;div&gt;.
如果我用一个或一个更好的元素，请不要对我做出评价。
Don't judge me if I use a list or
something like that a better element.
但使用 &lt;div&gt; 是因为它是代码测试，而我的时间有限。
But am using &lt;div&gt; because it's
a code test and I'm limited on time.
我加了这个图像，你可以用这个名字不重要。
I just added the image, you can use
the name doesn't really matter.
我添加类列表，我正在添加类的项名。
I add the class list,
I'm adding the item name of the class.
我不知道我只是这样做的
Don't know I'm gonna do with
that I just did it just in case.
我要回来的元素是我创造的
And I'm returning that
element that I created.
所以我做的下一件事就是我创造了这个功能
So next thing I did was after I
created this function was I created
文档片段。
a document fragment.
这就是如果你给出一个可靠的代码测试或者回答这样一个被解决的代码测试。
This is if you're giving a solid code test
or answering a solved code test like this.
创建文档片段 cubz ，它会创建元素的副本。
Create a document fragment cuz what that
does is it creates a copy of an elements.
然后我就能把东西插在那个片段里
And then I can just insert things
into that fragment piece of document.
一旦我完成插入，我就把它附加到实际的避孕套上。
And then once I'm done inserting,
I append that to the actual dom.
使用文档片段的优点是
What's the advantage of
using document fragments,
而不是直接向它附加
instead of just appending
straight into it?
我也可以的
Cuz I also could have
做了些什么
done something like.
在 forEach 中，我可以将 this.brute.append 子代。
In the forEach I could have
said this.brute.append child.
然后我就可以打这个电话了
And then I could have called this.
我希望那是有用的
I hope that works.
我本可以做点什么的
I could have done something like that.
但为什么我要用一个文件片段呢 ?
But why did I use a document fragment?
有人吗有人吗
Anybody, anybody at all?
>> 您正在追加一簇时间。
&gt;&gt; You're appending a bunch of times.
> > 是。 > And
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
&gt;&gt; And
你只是在追加一次
this one you're just appending once.
> > 这有什么意义呢 ?
&gt;&gt; So what are the implications of that?
>> 你在做更多的事情，当你追加的时候，
&gt;&gt; You're doing more stuff with the dom,
when you're appending, so
一些表演。
some sort of performances.
> > 嗯，那就对了。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, that's exactly right.
如果我们要追加这就意味着我们会不断更新 DOM 这意味着
If we're appending, that means we're
constantly updating DOM which means it's
在表演的过程中它会退化
rerendering, between performances
it's gonna be degraded.
Versus 如果我只追加一次，就会呈现一次，然后我就完成了。
Versus if I only append once,
it's one render and then I'm done.
这就是我要找的东西
That's something I look for.
我希望人们能理解文件碎片
I want people to understand
document fragments or
只是不断地呈现给我们的表演所带来的影响
just the performance implications
of constantly rendering to the dom.
不是什么魔术
Not a magic trick.
这只是一种好的知识
It's just kind of good knowledge to have,
就像这样做的方式吗
in understanding like how
does rendering work?.
当我完成后，我将附加该子代，并将该文档片段附加到
And once I'm done, I append that child and
I append that document fragment in so
它是一个渲染
it's one render.
一旦我做到了，我就知道有一些怀疑论者。
Then once I was done, and just in case,
I know there's some skeptics out there.
这是我的控制台日志，我在执行此操作时抛出了很多错误。
This is my console log, I threw a lot
of errors while I was doing this.
我正在写这个课程，我还是写错误。
And I'm giving this course and
I still write errors.
我打开开发者工具，以了解抛出了哪些错误。
I open my developer tools just to
see what errors are getting thrown.
这才是真正的生活没人是完美的
This is real life, no one's perfect.
所以我干的最后一件事就是我有点麻烦
So the last thing I did was I ran a little
bit of trouble cuz I had to remember how
事件侦听器已工作。
event listeners worked.
但我向 root 用户添加了事件侦听器，然后提取了目标。
But I added an event listener to the root
and then I extracted the target.
目标是当您具有事件侦听器时正在单击的对象
And the target is the thing that is being
clicked on when you have an event listener
或单击事件侦听器。
or click event listener.
现在，我说要删除，我也要查清楚，文件删除件。
And now, I said remove, which I have to
look up as well, document remove element.
我应该知道但我应该知道
Just .remove, I should probably
should have known that but
我也得去看看
I had to look it up too.
但我把它添加到根和
But the reason why I
added it to the root and
而不是实际的孩子本身，我也可以做，
not the actual child element itself,
which I also could have done,
是事件代表团，而这就是事件代表团的样子。
was event delegation and
this is what event delegation looks like.
这意味着有一个事件侦听器，而不是我在这里所拥有的许多项。
It means there's one event listener rather
than however many items I have here.
用这种方式来思考是好事
And it's good to think
in terms of that way,
因为说我有 1000 件事的清单
because let's say I had
a list of 1,000 things.
你会看到你的表演速度非常缓慢
You'd see your performance
slow dramatically down.
当然，当我单击它时，它会从列表中除去所有内容，一次一次。
And of course, when I click it removes
everything from the list, one at a time.
这是代码测试的示例。
That's an example of a code test.
我认为这是一个对一般 UI 工程师的合理的密码测试。
And I consider it a fairly reasonable
code test for a general UI engineer.
如果我需要一个角工程师的话我可能会问一个角度的问题
Now if I needed a, say angular engineer,
I might ask a question in angular and
你可以用这种方式解决，或者做出反应之类的事情。
have you solve that that way, or
react or something like that.
如果我是说我要一个 UI 工程师，就不要有具体的框架，
If I'm saying I want a UI engineer, don't
really have specific framework in mind,
我会问这样的一个问题
I'll ask a question like this sure.
因为我不需要语言或框架
Because I don't necessarily
want a language or framework or
一个特定于图书馆的专家
a library specific expert.
如果我们切换到一起，一个刚刚推出的新框架。
Cuz what if we switch to,
what's a new framework that just came out.
>> Svelte。
&gt;&gt; Svelte.
> > 嗯，让我们说我们切换到 Svelte ，而不是 React 或类似的内容。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, let's say we switch to Svelte
instead of React or something like that.
所有这些 React 的知识都是一文不值的
Then all that React knowledge,
it's worthless.
所以我要一个普通的 UI 工程师。
So I want a general UI engineer.
如果你能理解这种情况，我就知道你可以学到其他东西。
If you understand something like this,
then I know you can learn something else.
但如果你把整个职业生涯都花在一个框架上
But if you only spend your entire career
coding one framework, you're probably not
你的想法会很灵活也许这不是我要找的
gonna be as flexible in your thinking,
that's might not be what I'm looking for.
干得好你们都完成了
Nice job, all of you who completed it.
如果有点挑战性别担心因为你有那么多人
If it was a little challenging, don't
worry, it throws people because you get so
用于图书馆的所有重型提升
used to all the heavy lifting
that the libraries do for
你回旧学校可以给你打个圈
you that going back old school
can throw you for a loop.
但一旦你看到它希望你能明白这不是太棘手
But once you see it, hopefully you
understand it's not too tricky.
我也没问过要创建一个 Web 工作者，开始多线程，或者
And I didn't ask anything like create
a web worker and start multi threading or
任何类似的事情
anything like that.
只有你能看到的东西
Just things you can look up.
那是一个手机屏幕。
So that was a phone screen.